gamingsites100.com 2009-06-17

# Privacy PolicyGaming Sites Top 100 - Toplist | WoW Private Servers | WoW Gold

The privacy of our visitors to GamingSites100.com is important to us. 

At GamingSites100.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit GamingSites100.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to our site to managed your listings.

We also use third party advertisements on GamingSites100.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by [JenSense](http://www.jensense.com/)

Have your own gaming website? Join us today and get thousands more visitors per month! 

7282 sites in our database. IN/OUT resets every month.  
Time until reset: 13 days, 11 hours and 19 min.

© 2007 [GamingSites100.com](http://www.gamingsites100.com/) \- All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy.
